homejobsearchengine.com 2011-05-25

# Untitled Document

**Introduction**  

You may be referred to as User. The terms 'You' or 'User' includes you and any of your owners, employees, partners, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, attorneys, agents, heirs, and assigns.  

We may be referred to as Provider. The terms 'Us,' 'We,' or 'Provider' includes and our owners, employees, subsidiaries, independent contractors, agents, attorneys, and assigns.  

The website Homejobsearchengine.com may be referred to as the terms 'Homejobsearchengine.com' or 'Site'.  

By using this website, are agreeing to let the 'Site' 'Homejobsearchengine.com' operated by 'US' the 'Provider' to collect and use personal information from 'you' the 'User'. Do not use the website Homejobsearchengine.com if you have not read and agreed to this privacy policy.  

We respect your interest in your privacy and as a result we have created this informational disclosure as a commitment to your privacy and security. This privacy policy explains how the website collects information from its users, visitors, Users or anyone who visits the website and how this information is used. This may include those that have not purchased any of our products. It is very important you read this Privacy Policy carefully or, leave and do not continue to use this site.  

**Personal Information Collected and How It Is Used**  

We may collect your personal information from you like your name, email, address, phone number, or fax. We collect this information when you purchase a product or service from us, request information by email or newsletter, or actively communicate with the Site or us.  

We collect and use personal information for many purposes, including but not limited to, billing; product and service fulfillment; to better understand our User needs; to provide a better website, products and services; to communicate with Users and potential Users regarding our products and services and third party products and services.  

Generally, your private information will only be disclosed to our owners, employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, partners, affiliates, attorneys, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on our behalf or request. This general rule, and disclosures in specific situations, is more particularly described below.  

**Children's Privacy**  

You must be at least 18 years old to access this website. We do not direct this website to persons under 18, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.  

**Information Collected by our ISP**  

The hosting provider for this Internet site (as with any Internet site) has the ability to record various information, including domain name, pages accessed, date and time of access, web browser type and computer operating system, and referring information, and to disclose this information. This is most commonly done by providing access to raw server logs. For more information you should perform an Internet search on 'server logs' or 'raw server logs.' We may have access to our raw server logs and access reports prepared by our hosting provider.  

**Non Personally Identifiable Information and How It Is Used**

We may collect non personally identifiable information including but not limited to browser type, site browsing patterns, demographic information, and other non personally identifiable information. We use this information to track user patterns, and improve the quality of the site for you. We hold the right to share this information with authorized third parties to further increase user satisfaction.  

**Financial Information for Billing Purposes**  

We sell products and services. When sales are made financial information must be disclosed. This information can include any number of facts you are asked to provide, but most commonly includes your name, financial / credit card information, billing address, and email address. Generally, this purchase information will be provided by you to a third party payment processor and we do not receive your financial / credit card information.  

In the event we do receive financial / credit card information, we will not disclose it to anyone unless disclosure is required by law or a court order, or unless disclosure is required to address an issue implicated by the financial transaction. If you claim that your financial information was used to make a purchase you did not authorize, details about the financial transaction may be disclosed to law enforcement and anyone else we deem necessary to address the matter.  

By Becoming a User, using the site, or purchasing a product or service, you are consenting to sharing your personal identifiable financial information with our payment service providers or any third parties we determine necessary to process your transactions. These third parties could include the banking institutions, credit card companies, or merchants used to process the transaction.  

**Confirming Your Order**  

After confirming the purchase of one of our products or services, you consent to let us share or sell your Personally Identifiable Information like your email address, name and phone number to third party companies offering additional products and services which include but are not limited to personal coaching and consulting services. If you do not want us to share your personally identifiable information with third parties, please do not order any products and services from this site or contact us at the email listed below. We will not be held responsible for the third parties products, services, information, website or offers as well as how the third parties use your personally identifiable information.  

**Use of eMail Addresses and other Contact Information To Subscribe To Services**  

An important part of our services include being able to provide information to you. As a result, you expressly consent to receiving communications from us and approved third parties via email, fax, telephone, mail, or any other delivery method.  

As a User you are agreeing to receive information about the product or service you purchased. This may include, but is not limited to, information about product and service updates, new features, or information we believe you may find interesting.  

We may also send you information about other products and services our company and authorized third party have to offer.  

We will not sell, provide, or transfer your email address, name or phone number to anyone who is not an authorized third party.  

We may allow advertising to our Users, or engage in joint ventures, which result in you receiving offers or information from selected third parties. These third party offers are not operated by us the provider of this site. We will not be held responsible for the third parties business practices, or the products, services, and information, provided by these third parties. We also will not be held responsible for how these companies use your personally identifiable information when using or purchasing a product or services from any third party as a result of an advertisement and joint venture. However, once you actively participate with a third party, you understand that we will have no control over how these third parties use your information as well as how to stop receiving emails from the third parties.  

Signing up to receive emails from Homejobsearchengine.com requires a double opt-in confirmation subscription. This means the first email we send out must be activated inside your email account. By doing this, you are consenting to receive emails and promotions from us the Provider. You have the choice to stop receiving emails from Homejobsearchengine.com at the bottom of each email we send out or by contacting us at the email address listed below.  

**Shopping On Other Sites**  

On our site, you may find references, advertisements, promotions or links to other third parties offering similar products, services or information. It is entirely up to you to decide if you would like to purchase these products and services or sign up to receive information from these third parties. We will not be held responsible for what these third parties do with your personally identifiable information.  

We hold the right to terminate any references, advertisements, promotions or links on the site for any third party products, services and information at any time.  

**Emails and Newsletters**  

When you make a purchase or use this site, we may collect personally identifiable information like your name and email address. You are required to double opt-in to our email list or newsletter to receive information from us and by doing this you are giving us consent to send you information we feel necessary. If you share this personally identifiable information with us, we may use this information to send related offers you may or may not have interest in, from both us and other authorized third parties. You have the choice to opt-out of on every email and newsletter we send out if you wish to stop receiving these offers. You can also email us at the email listed below to stop receiving these promotions.  

**Testimonials**  

If you would like to submit a testimonial, you must be aware that any personal identifiable information you provide to the site like your name, email, city or state you live, or website address can be displayed anywhere on this site. This information could be obtained by unauthorized third parties and we will not be held responsible for the personally identifiable information you decide to submit to this site. We will also not be held responsible for what the third parties may do with the information you provide as a testimonial.  

**Identification of Purchasers**  

If you purchase one of our products or services, you authorize us to use your name and identification information in advertising or promotions.  

We also use personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.  

**Google Adsense**  

We may display ads from Google. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other website's in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  

**Cookies**  

Cookies may be used to keep track of referred affiliate commissions and to monitor access to our website. You consent to any future use of cookies for testing purposes and the use of cookies for publicly available data to gather statistics for the purpose of determining which search engines, referring sites, key words, etc., bring visitors to our website, which pages visitors are most interested in, what web browsers are used, etc. Various providers may be used for this purpose. The purpose is obtain information that will help promote the website, make the website more interesting and useful to visitors, and to identify areas where improvement is needed.  

Additionally, various third party information suppliers and other entities that provide information for this website, or for use by us, may use cookies. Examples include, but are not necessarily limited to billing providers, third party advertisers, and third party resources we promote.  

**Community Forums, Chat Rooms, and Message Boards**  

To provide our users with better service and experience, the site may use Forums, Chat Rooms or Message Boards. Submitting information to these community functions, you are potentially exposing your personally identifiable information to unauthorized third parties. You should exercise caution when submitting information to any Forum, Chat Room, or Message Board. We will not be held responsible for third parties illegally obtaining information from you. If you suspect someone is obtaining user information for unsolicited acts, please contact us at the email address below.  

**Links**  

This site contains links to other third parties website's Although we do our best to protect all our users, we cannot insure or be completely aware of any security issues of other website's or any domain forwarding practices that may result in Viruses, Trojans, Worms, and lost or stolen information. Because we do not have a way to detect and screen for Viruses, Trojans, Worms, or other deceiving practices by other website's, it is up to you to make sure that you have taken the appropriate steps to protect you and your system from these types of illegal and destructive acts.  

**Disclosure by Necessity**  

Private information may be disclosed if required by a court order, statute, law, or regulation.  

Information is subject to disclosure to address a claim that you are violating the terms of any agreement pertaining to your use of your use this website or our products or services, or rights of any third party.  

Information is also subject to disclosure if we believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring an action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering (either intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, your rights or property, other users of our website, products or services, or anyone else.  

As we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company, or be bought by another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred assets.  

Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which we maintain facilities or conduct operations. By using our website, products and services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.  

After your account becomes inactive your information may remain in our databases, computers, and archives, and cannot reasonably be expunged.  

**  
Copyright Information**  

This product is copyrighted. All rights reserved.  

Our information may not be copied in part or in full without our express written consent.  

**Notices for Copyright Violations**  

Our website and services may allow others to add files or content to our website or services. Links may also be added to website's that are controlled by others. This may be done automatically and without our review.  

It is our policy, to suspend or terminate the accounts of users who may intentionally or repeatedly infringe the copyrights others. Whether we choose to do so is entirely within our discretion.  

**Changes To Privacy Policy**  

This Privacy Policy may not be modified or amended orally, impliedly, or in any manner not set forth in writing or permitted by this Privacy Policy.  

This Privacy Policy may be amended by us at any time and without notice, but only by amending this Privacy Policy as posted on this website, unless otherwise agreed to in a writing signed by both of us.  

Any amendments will become effective 30 days after being posted on the website, unless circumstances require that a change be immediately implemented. As a condition for this Privacy Policy you agree to periodically check this Privacy Policy posted at this page.  

You agree that your continued use of our product or service after that date will constitute your consent and acceptance of the amendment and Privacy Policy.  

Effective Date: July 22nd, 2010

Modified: May 16th, 2011  

*Notice* Anyone who uses text, images, our trademarks or copyrighted material from Homejobsearchengine.com without written consent will be prosecuted under The Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DCMA).

The entire content of this website is Copyright © 2010 by Homejobsearchengine.com. All rights Reserved.
